cointrader.biz 2014-09-06

# (575.77) Cointrader - Bitcoin Exchange - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Last updated: [December 1, 2013]

## General

Cointrader and its affiliates (hereinafter, "Cointrader", "we", "us" or "our") are dedicated to protecting and respecting your privacy. We protect your personal information in accordance with the Privacy Act of Canada, the Privacy Act of British Columbia, and other applicable laws.

This Privacy Policy, together with our Terms of Use, governs the collection, storage, and transmission of Personal Information as well as non-identifiable information.

Personal Information includes any and all information that may be used to identify an individual.

## Collection of Personal Information

We may collect Personal Information when you register an account, use our services, perform transactions on our site, or contact us for support. The types of Personal Information we collect may include:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Phone Number
  * Email Address
  * Financial Information
  * Photo Identification
  * Trade History

You are free at anytime to remove consent for the use and disclosure of personal information, other than as required by our legal obligations. This may result in you being unable to access certain products or services which require such information.

We seek your consent for the collection or disclosure of personal information unless the collection, use or disclosure without consent is authorized or required by law. We may assume consent where you provide information for a clear purpose.

## Use of Personal Information

We may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:

  * Opening an account with our Site and allowing access to use our services
  * Conducting transactions on our Site
  * Support and contact inquiries
  * Research and improvement of the platform (e.g. layout, performance, implementing new services, etc.)
  * As required for regulatory and legal purposes
  * Providing information to you about our services, changes, and critical news - only with your expressed consent

We will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that for which it has been provided, unless required by law.

## Disclosure of Personal Information

For the limited purposes described above, we may disclose the Personal Information provided to us with:

  * Affiliates, agents, and representatives
  * Trusted service providers
  * Contractors
  * Financial institutions
  * Insurance companies
  * Other companies in case of corporate re-organization
  * Law enforcement and regulatory agencies, if required by law

All third-parties with access to Personal Information shall be required to protect this Personal Information and are only given permission to carry out the services they are performing for you or us, unless otherwise required or permitted by law. Our contracts with third-parties will require terms of greater or equal protection than those required under this Privacy Policy, for all Personal Information disclosed.

## Digital Information

We may collect some information about your computer for system administration and security. Such information will not be personally identifiable, including: 

  * IP address
  * Operating system
  * Browser type and version

We also use browser cookies for unique identification of your computer. These are stored on your own computer and allow us to improve the effectiveness of our services and overall user experience. We may, for example, use cookies to determine access problems to particular pages of the Site, or provide personalized experiences for our services.

We occasionally use third party service providers to assist in the maintenance and improvement of our Site. These services help us better understand the needs and interests of our clients in order to provide a better experience and set of services. These providers may also place cookies on your hard drive which will inform us regarding the use of our products and services in aggregate reports. Any information collected by our service providers will be restricted by contract for the sole purpose of assisting Cointrader.

Use of this Site and its services implies agreement with the digital policies set above.

## Security and Protection of Information

We have implemented strict security procedures governing the storage and transmission of Personal Information in order to prevent theft, loss, disclosure, alteration, or unauthorized access. Some of our procedures include: 

  * SSL 256 bit encryption for data transmission
  * Encryption of Backups
  * Limited access to production data
  * Ongoing malware, SQL Injection, XSS, and CSRF scanning

All Personal Information is considered confidential and treated as such. Only authorized personnel are granted access to information, as required to fulfill tasks for our services. Our security measures are periodically reviewed to stay in line with technical and legal developments.

Retention of Personal Information is held only as long as reasonably required for business or legal purposes. When no longer required, we remove identifying information or destroy the information altogether. 

## Modification and Access of Personal Information

Cointrader clients have the right to access, correct, update, delete, or destroy Personal Information under the control of Cointrader, with some exceptions. We will honor requests except under the following circumstances:

  * Where the information would reveal personal information about another individual
  * Where information could reveal confidential business information
  * Where the information is held for mediation
  * Where other legal obligations prevent the disclosure of such information

Requests can be sent by email: support@Cointrader.com

Some detailed reports or physical copies may be subject to a fee.

## Links

We may, from time-to-time, provide links to other sites or third parties. This privacy policy is only valid in relation to this Site and its services, as specified above. Such third party sites are not under our control. By visiting them you agree that we are not responsible or liable, in whole or in part, for any of products, services, actions, content, policies, damages, losses, failures, problems, or any other activity, related to or arising from those sites. We strongly encourage you to take precautions and become informed before engaging any third party or organization.

## Modifications

At our sole discretion, our terms, policies, disclosures, features, content, information, promotions, services, and products may be modified, updated, removed, and supplemented at any time with or without prior notice. When Privacy Policy changes occur, we will take reasonable steps to notify users through notices on this site, amending this policy, or direct contact through email.

## Contact Us

Should you have any questions, concerns, comments, or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or practices related to using our services, please contact us through email or telephone:

E-Mail: shane@cointrader.net

Phone: 1 (877) 814-7460

Last updated: [December 1, 2013]
